Jena Expeditions! Jena Explorers!
Tamirige and Yasumoriaka.
Yes, please.
Jena Explorers!
You're wearing something today.
What happened to your face, Mr. Gecko?
Rabbit gecko.
A rabbit, you mean.
It's already on the back.
Today...
E-bins first sale in 2023
I've been wondering...
With only a few days left in this year
but it's coming to an end
Which means the first sale is coming soon
It's here again this year
That's right!
Here is an enlarged panel of the advertisement.
Today, while looking at this panel
I'd like to introduce the first sale information
I'd like to ask you two to introduce the first sale of Ebbins.
Yes, sir!
Yes! So, I would like to introduce you to the first sale of 2023 Inbiz!
Please do!
First of all, it's important to know when we're going to do it.
April 2nd, Monday
And January 3, Tuesday.
Ah, ah, nyo?
No? Yes?
The time is a little bit different.
The time is a little different.
January 2nd, we open at 7:30
On February 3, the store opens at 8:30.
If you have something you want, please line up!
Some people come as early as the day before!
Amazing, isn't it?
On January 2nd, we will be open only on January 2nd.
We, Iginari, Oku, Rinkyu, and
Rinkyu, and Furen the rabbit
Flemish Giant will welcome you!
Does that mean Flemish Giant will come only for rabbits?
It looks like it!
Is this a real rabbit?
Yes, it looks like it.
A real one-meter tall sasa will come.
Yes, yes, yes.
Today, we have a Flemish Giant, not a Flemish Giant.
It's not a Flemish Giant...
Not Mr. Flemish Giant...
But a bunny rabbit is here to play with us!
Oh, my gosh!
Here he comes!
That's great!
Sorry, I'm late.
This is Mr. Tama.
Tama?
Oh, oh, oh, Tama-san, Tama-san.
This is a two-month-old sea urchin.
He's too cute!
It's sea urchin time!
Sea urchin chicken!
Wow!
There's actually a sea urchin... on the same day.
Sea urchins!
We'll be here on both the 2nd and the 3rd.
Four times.
You can have a snack and a photo taken with the sea urchin.
Wow!
The first customer gets a rabbit meat tenderizer.
You'll have to work hard.
So you'll be working on the 2nd?
Don't say you're working.
We're in this together.
Please come and see the sea urchin and sometimes the sea urchin.
You've done a great job this year, too.
Here he is!
Mr. Toufuku, isn't it?
Yay!
So we're all rabbits now?
That's right... we're all rabbits... so we all have ears.
Where's Mr. Rest?
Where are the rests?
What are you doing?
He's pointing at the first sale.
It's the first sale!
I see...
Where have you been?
Here.
No, it's not!
This way.
Wow, your hair looks...
It's so fluffy.
It's like real.
I'm wearing a special Belle Ebeau.
It's true!
So cute!
Hey, you two.
It's very unusual, isn't it?
Are you going the cute route, 2023?
When it comes to rabbits... you can't avoid this place.
Rabbits are cute.Rabbits are cute.
I see.
I heard that you can see Tatsunen's humor by reading this QR code.
So I'd like you all to take a look at it!
From the Ibee's website
What do you think of New Year's?
Correct!
A goody bag!
Is it an educational program?
Speaking of New Year's, what do you think of fukubukuro?
This year, too, Eavins' fukubukuro
are very gorgeous!
There's a lot to choose from!
Yay!
Located on the B11th floor of Eavins
Muscle Man Shop
I had the pleasure of shooting for YouTube!
Thank you very much!
Muscle Man grab bag
The most expensive one is 31,000 yen!
What is this?
I wonder if it's for Muscle Man.
It's got the characters until March 19th.
Leary... that's right... it's a dream come true.
I see.
Boo-boo... imagine why it's so expensive while you're imagining it.
You don't open it imagining what it's all about, how fun it would be, but hey...
There are three vans, so you can buy them all, or you can choose the most expensive one, or you can decide for yourself.
You can buy all three vans, or you can choose the most expensive one, or you can decide for yourself.
You can talk!
I'm going to do the same thing three times at the earphone and headphone specialty store Iya Honzan
I'm sure you've been to a lot of events and Tohoku-san has a big corner right now and we're selling a limited number of goody bags
I'm sure you'll be able to find a lot of information about the limited edition fukubukuro.
I'm sure that means you can't cut it up here, right?
I'm sure you'll be able to find a good deal on a limited number of them.
I see... the original Endochene goodie bag...
3 End-Chain t-shirts, 5 badges, and a tote bag.
3 End-Chain t-shirts, 5 badges and a tote bag.
What kind of art do you have?
You're getting good, either me
I was thinking maybe choke
Hey...
Boo hoo, Aria.
This, this, this...
I know you're going to deploy the brake catcher, but you didn't tell me how to use it. The captain said he'd be there, so I thought I'd give him a little something.
But it's a present for the captain. And I bought this.
I bought this for the captain.
And this tote bag... and this set.
How cheap!
So cheap! Too cheap!
And it comes with something, right, Mr. Asma?
That's right.
If you buy this, you get a dining coupon for E Finish.
One to eat at any eatery in the building.
One free meal ticket.
You're already eating. Already eating?
What are you eating?
I'm eating at the crepe stand.
What's with the manners?
It's not polite.
There's more, too.
There's a lot of other goodies in there, too.
Check them all out!
Please check them all out!
Bye-bye, Den!
I'm so happy!
Aa!
Yasumuri!
Poka-pyon!
Babylon!
Youth try your luck and grab the cash with the winning ticket!
Eeeee!
What? Did you get it? Really?
Oh, no!
There's two ways to get it.
The first 1,000 people to arrive will get a chance to participate.
At the Garden Terrace on the 4th floor.
Purchase a one-entry sheet for 3,000 yen or more
you can grab a prize once.
And if you win, you get one more catch for 5 days.
you will be able to get one more time for the next 5 days!
Eeeeee!
In other words, you can grab it twice for a maximum of over 3000 yen!
Simply put, that's a lot of money, isn't it?
Simply put, you're getting paid like crazy!
I thought I'd let you two see what it's really like today.
Really? Yes! Pocket change!
I thought we'd try one of those cash-and-carry things.
Is it heavy? It's very heavy.
You'll have to do the luxury version I prepared for you today.
Yes, sir.
I prepared the box only for today.
Let's take a look inside.
It looks like this.
Wow!
If you grab this and put it in the measuring device over here, you can see how much you get.
The amount will be displayed.
Let's go!
Wow!Wow!
Loud!
It's so deep!
But it's hard to get it out!
I know, right? I can grab it, but I can't...
Oh, no! Hang in there!
Oh! I feel like...
Aah!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
You're really poking out!
On the edge!
That's one of them!
No, it's not!
It's just what I'm grabbing!
Oh! That one!
Go, go, go, go!
I'm going in!
Ooh!
Great, great, great, great, great, great!
That's great!
He said 3,000!
That's great, great, great, great, great!
Oh! Here we go!
Still going?
Oh! Oh, my God!
Oh! Steval!
What?
That's it?
Is it done? Is it the last one?
2,800 yen?
Oh, man!
Oh, man! That's more than I expected!
I thought I didn't look for it at all.
That's right! I really don't know, how can you grab something like this with a human hand?
What if you have big hands?
Maybe someone with smaller hands will have an advantage.
Oh, this is it!
The one who takes it out like this wins.
So if you come with a couple...
It's better for the wife to do it than the husband.
I see.
Yes! Definitely better!
Then, God Hand Waka! Let's go!
How is it?
Great!
Great?
I've never grabbed so many pennies in my hands.
That's for sure.
My hands are full.
It's just a matter of getting it out, isn't it?
Yeah, that's right.
The trick is...
Oh, that's great.
That's great.
Oh!
Ha-ha-ha-ha
It's making a lot of noise.
Did I go?
No, no, no, no.
I totally went over by a good margin.
It's okay. It's okay.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
It's still growing.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Oh, there it goes.
That's great, that's great, that's great, that's great.
Oh, wow.
I'm going for it.
Come on. Come on.
Ooh.
There you go.
Wow.
Yay.
Sixty-two fifty.
Wow!
I'm so happy!
Amazing!
So much for one person!
This is amazing!
This is great!
But it's a luxury edition.
If you don't win the first prize
If you don't win, you can't try this.
But even if you do...
But even so, it's amazing.
So, I've actually tried it now.
It's a lot of fun and exciting.
I mean, really...
When you make a purchase, please take out your receipt.
Take out your receipt
and grab it!
Pull out your receipt and win!
and you're going to win a lot of money!
That's so cool!
Let's do it!
Wow.
This way.Click here
Onoya Shimamaki Suisan Kakeru Yen Copper Chain Original Canned Food
Yay!
La la la la la la la la la!
Super cool!
It's like it just grew out of me.
Amazing!
We were coming over.
They were even showing us around.
You did the Tohoku cans for us, right?
Yes, sir.
You must be Ki-ya.
Thank you for all your help.
Yes, we're always grateful.
This Kanazawa mackerel simmered in miso is delicious.
I hope you all get it!
Buy more than 1 yen in a can at the entrance of the Sendai-bound river?
That's not so easy!
What are you talking about?
You don't sell anything for 1 yen!
Buy something!
Anything is fine. Even 10 yen gum.
I see.
Umaibo?
Can I get a can of Kikiya's mackerel stewed in miso?
You can have it.
That's so good!
It's so good!
What a bargain!
It's great!
2023 Hatsumemu Live will be held!
We've been doing this every year, too.
The event will be held at the 10th rooftop stage.
January 2nd is the day!
Of course, we, Inari Tohoku
We will perform again this year!
And I Spy!
Seiza Hyakkei Great!
Colorful Scream!
Four groups on the 2nd!
And on January 3rd, Ebi Dancender!
Ebi Dansender!
And Mr. Cross Border.
Mr. Blair Cool.
Mr. No Name.
Mr. BMK's five groups.
I see.
I hear they're splitting up the women and men in two or three days.
I'm looking forward to the Hatsuyumu Live!
Let's make it exciting!
Let's go for it!
Okay, everyone!
And the first sale of Eby's in 2023.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye!
Have a Happy New Year!
Happy New Year!